ANDREW GRANT



andrewgrant2009@hotmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/andrewjbgrant



Berlin, Germany

SKILLS

- Strong Communication
- **Problem-Solving**
- Adaptability
- **Time Management**
- **Team work**
- **Continuous Learning**

QUALIFICATIONS

Le Wagon Coding school

Full-stack Web Development Bootcamp

JUN-DEC 2022

- · Developed Web applications using Ruby on Rails, Working with technologies such as JavaScript, HTML, CSS and SQL.
- · Took part in Daily stand-ups and code reviews throughout
- · Collaborated within a team of three on group projects to build two full-stack web apps.

CODING SKILLS

- JavaScript
- · Ruby on Rails
- React
- TypeScript
- **CSS**
- Postgres SQI

PROFILE

As a passionate Chef with a strong affinity for technology, I am incredibly excited about the opportunity to apply my culinary expertise and embrace my burgeoning interest in web development.

I am driven by a genuine curiosity and eagerness to delve into this dynamic field. By combining my culinary problem-solving skills, effective communication abilities, and customer-centric mindset, I aim to contribute to the success of Intercom's users while continuously expanding my knowledge in the ever-evolving world of technology.

EXPERIENCE

Sous Chef (Feb 2021 - October 2023)

Gazzo Pizza, Berlin

- · Assisted with day-to-day operations, working efficiently and productively with all team members.
- · Planned and directed high-volume preparation in fast-paced environment.
- Initiated training for new team members on to improve productivity and increase workflows.

Private Chef (June 2020 - Nov 2020)

- · Provided catering services to small gatherings and different events.
- · Managed time efficiently in order to complete all tasks within deadlines.

Chalet Chef (Nov 2019 - March 2020)

Highlife Ski and Snowboard, Mereibel

- · Customer facing role, interacted daily with guests, addressed their needs and ensured satisfaction.
- · Proved successful working within tight deadlines and a fast-paced environment.
- Exercised leadership capabilities by successfully communicating with other staff.
- Required effective communication, adaptability and creativity.